<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<document>
  <paragraph>Part 1 – The Memory Rekindled</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The steam lingered thick in the &lt;i&gt;ofuro&lt;/i&gt;, curling in delicate tendrils along the wooden ceiling, clinging to the walls, and pooling in gentle eddies at the rim of the tub. Misaki stepped out with care, water trailing in rivulets down her bare skin, collecting at her ankles before falling in soft, steady taps against the ceramic tiles. The towel she'd draped over the stool awaited her—still warm, steeped in the room's lingering heat.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She wrapped the towel tightly around herself, drawing the edges snug across her chest before reaching for a smaller one to gather her hair. With practiced ease, she twisted it into a loose coil and perched it atop her head. Her hand moved instinctively toward the place where her twin tails had always been—only to falter, fingers brushing at empty air. The severed strands now lay folded inside another towel by the sink. The motion startled her, a phantom reflex—like reaching for an appendix that had only just been cut away.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her reflection wavered in the small mirror mounted on the wall, its surface still blurred with a fine sheen of moisture. She wiped at it absently, clearing a streak wide enough to reveal her own eyes—soft teal, framed by the hazelnut strands now peeking out from beneath the towel. Saitō-san had mentioned he would have contact lenses delivered to disguise the striking colour of her pupils. But she couldn’t remember if he’d said where they would be. She let the thought drift, her gaze lingering on the girl in the mirror.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She looked… different. Softer, almost. Her fingertips brushed her cheeks, tracing the line of her jaw. It wasn’t just the hair—it was the stillness, the quiet that seemed to hang over this place like morning fog. In the city, even silence was loud: sirens bleeding through concrete, the low rumble of traffic, the distant whine of planes overhead. But here, silence felt real. It breathed with the murmur of the sea far below, waves rising and falling like a slow heartbeat against the cliff. Wind threaded through the bamboo grove, sighing through leaves and brushing against the house in soft exhalations. From beneath the eaves, a single &lt;i&gt;suzumushi&lt;/i&gt; sang its bell-like tune, delicate and tentative. A lone &lt;i&gt;fūrin&lt;/i&gt; clinked faintly in the breeze, its sound barely more than a breath. This silence was different. It settled into her bones—no longer something to drown out, but something to feel.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The floor creaked softly beneath her as she stepped back from the mirror, the warmth of the bath still clinging to her skin. She cast one last glance around the room—the wooden beams overhead, the lingering scent of cedar and steam woven into the walls. Then, with a quiet motion, she pushed open the swing door and stepped into the hall, where the air met her bare shoulders—warm, crisp, and bracing against her damp skin.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Only now, in the hush that followed, did she pause—hand still resting on the knob. It struck her: this door was different. Not just in feel, but in presence. It swung outward on hinges, solid and modern, the kind of door you’d find in a city apartment or a hospital ward. All the others in the house had been &lt;i&gt;shōji&lt;/i&gt;—delicate, sliding panels that moved like breath. This one didn’t belong.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She hadn’t paid too much attention to it before. Then again, she’d barely made it inside that day. Her stomach had been cramping, her urgency sharp and overwhelming. There’d been no time for observation, no room for curiosity. Just pain and panic and a desperate search for the toilet.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Now, in the quiet after the bath, the door stood out like a puzzle piece from the wrong box.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Why only here?</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The thought lingered as she let the door ease shut behind her with a soft click. Probably nothing. And yet, the contrast it drew—between then and now, between chaos and stillness—etched itself into her awareness like a ripple beneath calm water.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She inhaled deeply, letting the silence settle around her once more. No alarm bells. No pressure. Just a moment suspended in the hush of a house that had asked nothing of her. </paragraph>
  <paragraph>And in that quiet, she remembered the suitcase. It waited by the &lt;i&gt;genkan&lt;/i&gt;, just where she had left it when she arrived. It sat alone, untouched, its edges slightly scuffed from years of travel. She padded across the tatami, her feet silent against the woven straw, and knelt beside it, fingertips brushing the latches before she clicked them open. The hinges creaked softly as the lid rose, revealing neatly folded clothes and small necessities.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her fingers hovered over a few options before settling on a light grey nightshirt—the softest one she owned, somewhere between a long tee and a summer sleep dress. She had packed it thinking it would be enough. In Tokyo, it always was. She slipped the towel from her head, and then the one wrapped around her body. Draped them over the edge of the suitcase, and ran her fingers through her damp hair before pulling the nightshirt over her head.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The relief barely lasted.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Within seconds, the air wrapped around her like a wet sheet—thick, heavy, relentless. The fabric clung to her back, damp at the hem, already sticking to her thighs.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Too hot. Way too hot.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She yanked it off with a groan and tossed it aside. Sweat prickled at her collarbones.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>&lt;i&gt;Hokkaido never did this to me&lt;/i&gt;, she thought, wiping her forehead. A breeze through the window, maybe a mosquito or two—but never this. Summer used to be her favourite season when she was a child.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>That changed in Tokyo. Autumn had taken over then—when the air began to bite and layers felt safe. It reminded her of Hokkaido summers. Familiar. Manageable.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>But here in Kamiyama Cove, with heat crawling beneath her skin, she already knew the truth. She was going to love winter.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The thought flickered through her mind—quick and vivid. While everyone else bundled in layers and tucked themselves under the &lt;i&gt;kotatsu&lt;/i&gt;, she’d be fine in a summer dress, the way she had been years ago. But now, in the thick of this summer, even her skin felt suffocating. She wanted to peel it off. And even then, it still wouldn’t be enough.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She reached into the suitcase again and pulled out a pair of panties. Slipping them on brought a faint sense of structure, a small anchor to normalcy. White and teal stripes, soft cotton, the edges bound in a thicker woven thread, and a tiny bow at the front—cute, comfortable. But not made for this heat. The fabric already clung more than it should have, the elastic warm against her hips.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She reached for a bra—habit more than necessity—and paused. Her fingers held the band for a moment, then tested the fit.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Loose. Far too loose.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>It still surprised her how much weight she had lost.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Still, she tried, hooking it in place and adjusting the straps. It gaped at the sides and sagged toward the base of her ribs. Worse than the fit was the heat—already blooming beneath the elastic. Her chest might have been flat—years of industry-mandated leanness had seen to that—but the sweat would still gather. It always did.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She exhaled through her nose, unhooked it, and let it fall on top of the discarded nightshirt. The air touched her skin without resistance. She stood in just her panties, hair damp from the bath, heat already returning in waves, and wondered how anyone managed to sleep through this.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>With a sigh, she reached back into the suitcase and pulled out her notepad. The pages were curled slightly at the corners from travel, but blank where they mattered. She flipped it open, pressed it flat against the edge of the suitcase, and began to write—short, slanted strokes in pencil.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>&lt;i&gt;Lighter panties. Shorts. Sleeveless sleep tee.&lt;/i&gt;</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She stared at the list for a moment, then glanced down at her chest. The skin there still felt flushed, faintly sticky.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She added a line beneath the others, almost as an afterthought.&lt;i&gt;Sports bra.&lt;/i&gt;At least until her regular ones fit again.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Misaki knelt in front of her suitcase after closing the notepad, sliding the pen back through the hoops. She held it between her lips to free both hands, reaching to fasten the case shut—but something stopped her.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her eyes flicked to the little wooden table near the &lt;i&gt;genkan&lt;/i&gt;—the one she’d barely noticed when she first walked in. A pair of slippers rested neatly beneath it. Atop the table sat a small clay pot, warm-toned and unglazed, with a butterfly delicately engraved into one side. From it rose a single flowering stem—an orchid plant, its arching spray of blossoms all in full bloom, delicate still in the heavy summer air.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>And there, beside the pot, was an envelope. It hadn’t been there before.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She froze, heart skipping once—not in fear, but recognition. The noise. That soft rustle she’d heard while outside, bracing herself in panic, her teal hair catching the last of the twilight through the toilet’s narrow window. She’d dismissed it at the time—too overwhelmed to think, too desperate to hide. She had rushed back inside and sealed herself away, shedding her colours, cocooned in steam and silence as she cut and dyed her hair. A metamorphosis, not born of beauty, but of necessity. And now, with her skin still warm from the bath and the panic long dissolved, the memory of that sound returned—fluttering back like wings testing open for the first time.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The footsteps… someone had been here. And they had left her something. It came rushing back—an echo she’d half-forgotten. The front gate creaking open. Footsteps crunching softly over the gravel. The slide of the &lt;i&gt;shōji&lt;/i&gt; door, quiet and deliberate. A pause. Then the door sliding shut again. More footsteps, retreating through the stones. The final clank of the metal gate. And then—silence.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her breath caught, fingers still hovering above the suitcase lid. The item by the flowerpot bore no name, no address—just a cream-coloured shell, perfectly pristine, as if placed there with deliberate care. Misaki swallowed. Her eyes flicked to the door—still shut, still unlocked. Just as she had left it.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her hand moved almost on its own, reaching for the missive, fingertips brushing its edge. It was heavier than she expected—the weight settling into her palm as she lifted it carefully from the table. Her heart thudded softly in her bare chest.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>As she turned it over, she saw it. The seal. Deep and deliberate—crimson wax pressed with the shape of a butterfly mid-flight, still and perfect.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>A chill threaded through her—light as breath, cutting clean through the heat. Her skin rose in goosebumps, arms tightening as if bracing against something unseen. Outside, the crickets sang in a blurred, continuous murmur, thick and close. The air was dense with summer, but she was sweating cold—fresh from the bath, yet already slick again. Beads of sweat traced slow paths down her ribs after slipping from the soft curves of her breasts, before falling to the floor in silent drops. Her chest went taut in the sudden chill, the peaks stiffening with the mix of sweat and air, alive to every breath.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her fingers trembled slightly as she held it. There were no other markings. No name. Just the smooth surface of cream paper, folded with precision and left as if it belonged there. Misaki stared down, her mind reaching for meaning, but the answers drifted just out of reach.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She glanced back at the door, then to her suitcase still open by the &lt;i&gt;genkan&lt;/i&gt;, clothes spilling slightly from the edges. Everything was as it should be. Everything—except this.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her thumb brushed the seal, testing its firmness. It did not give. She set the envelope back on the table, her hand lingering a moment longer before pulling away.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>And then she remembered. The &lt;i&gt;omamori&lt;/i&gt; that hung from the house keys Saitō-san had given her.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The image hit like a lightning bolt.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>&lt;i&gt;Could it be?&lt;/i&gt;</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She rushed back into the house, the envelope still in hand, nearly tripping over the wooden frame of the &lt;i&gt;shōji&lt;/i&gt; that separated the &lt;i&gt;genkan&lt;/i&gt; from the living room. The tatami gave beneath her as she dropped into &lt;i&gt;seiza&lt;/i&gt; out of instinct—body folding into the shape it had known since childhood—but pain flared the moment her knees touched the floor. A sting, low and sharp, bloomed beneath the skin where it had scraped raw the night before. She winced, but didn’t move.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Kneeling before the low table, she dug through the purse resting on top of it, breath catching as she searched. Lip balm. The cards Saitō-san had given her. The mobile phone she’d bought that morning. A half-crushed protein bar—from that first night, when he had returned with arms full of food and wouldn’t let her drift further into herself, no matter how little she wanted to eat.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She pushed aside the wrapper and felt it at last—cool metal, cotton thread. The old key. The one with the &lt;i&gt;omamori&lt;/i&gt; still dangling from its ring, its once-crisp tassel now softened and frayed with time.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She pulled it free, heart quickening, and turned it in her hand with care. Etched into the charm in faint, unmistakable lines—there it was.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She glanced between the key and the seal still resting beside her. Same wings. Same posture in flight. The match was too precise to be coincidence.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The very same butterfly—its wings spread in mid-air, frozen in perfect symmetry. Behind it, petals of cherry blossoms fell like whispers, each detail pressed into the wax with exquisite care. And in the embroidered fabric of the &lt;i&gt;omamori&lt;/i&gt;, the same image had been stitched in thread—the butterfly mid-flight, the blossoms drifting softly through the air.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>&lt;b&gt;神山の杜神社&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;. Kamiyama Grove Shrine. &lt;/b&gt;</paragraph>
  <paragraph>But the seal bore no writing. Just the image. Silent, exact, unmistakable.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She could almost see the wings move.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Misaki straightened slowly, drawing a breath that settled deep in her lungs. The stillness around her felt heavier now—charged, as if the envelope itself were watching her, waiting.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her stomach grumbled, sharp and sudden, pulling her back into her body. Not with urgency this time, but with need. Hunger.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She looked down at the sealed message once more. She would open it—but not yet.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Not like this. Not while her hands still trembled.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She needed to eat first. Let her thoughts settle. Let her body catch up to her breath.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Then… then she would face whatever was waiting inside.</paragraph>
  <paragraph></paragraph>
  <paragraph>Part 2 – The meal</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The kitchen was still—its surfaces untouched by clutter or modern convenience. Misaki stepped across the wooden floor, the faint creak of the boards echoing into the silence—only to be swallowed by the distant chorus of bell crickets outside, their cacophonous song serenading the wind as it caressed the waves far below the cliff, just visible through the window.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The air inside was thick with summer.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>It carried the scent of soot from the old &lt;i&gt;kamado&lt;/i&gt;, fused with the sharp, earthy sweetness of dried herbs that hung from the cedar beams—&lt;i&gt;shiso&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;sanshō&lt;/i&gt;, a few braided sprigs of something she couldn’t name. Beneath it, the sea crept in through the open window, lacing the room with salt. And threaded faintly through it all, the cool green hush of distant petrichor. It must have rained while she slept—the kind of light drizzle that deepened the scent of grass without ever waking her.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She stood there for a moment, breathing it in.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The house didn’t smell like Tokyo. It smelled like something older, more peaceful.</paragraph>
  <paragraph></paragraph>
  <paragraph></paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her gaze caught on the garlic hanging near the stove. It was fresh—&lt;i&gt;too&lt;/i&gt; fresh. A couple of cloves were missing from the lower bulb, plucked cleanly. And it wasn’t the last one on the stalk either. The one above had been taken first.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She turned her head, eyes falling to the cast iron pans on the wall-mounted rack. They were spotless, but not sterile. Their surface held the faint aroma of seasoning—of oil and something savoury, long-simmered, once warm. Not scrubbed away, just… lived in. The ghost of a meal still lingered, fragrant and fleeting.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Someone had cooked here.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Not weeks ago. Recently. They had peeled garlic. Used herbs. Let the flavours rise and cling to the metal. And then they had cleaned—quietly, thoroughly—restocked the soap, folded fresh towels.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>No one lived here. And yet… someone &lt;i&gt;had&lt;/i&gt;.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Not now. But not long ago, either. Not in passing. With intention.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She stood still, her hand resting against the edge of the counter, heart calm but watchful. It wasn’t fear that rose in her—just awareness. A deep, quiet sense that the house hadn’t been waiting for her in silence.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>A thought tugged at her.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She knelt down and opened the small fridge tucked beneath the counter—more out of idle curiosity than expectation. The seal hissed faintly as it gave.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Inside, the cool air wrapped around her fingers. And there, placed neatly on the middle shelf, was a ceramic bowl, covered in aluminium foil. Written across the foil in careful strokes of black permanent marker.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>&lt;b&gt;美咲&lt;/b&gt; Misaki.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her breath caught.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She stared, unmoving. The marker had bled slightly into the foil, the characters still dark and unmistakable. Someone had written her name—not Hatsune, not Miku. &lt;i&gt;Misaki&lt;/i&gt;. The name she hadn’t spoken aloud until only days ago.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Not hers by birth. Not hers by choice. A name Saitō had offered—gently, firmly—as the first step into her new life.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She reached in with both hands, cradling the bowl carefully. It was rather cold, weighty. Beneath the foil, a faint scent—something savoury, something real. She hadn’t eaten lunch. Not properly. And now it sat here, waiting for her, as if time had been folded gently around her arrival.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She leaned forward and looked deeper.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Two more bowls sat beside the first, each identical in size and shape, each sealed the same way—each labelled in that same steady hand.</paragraph>
  <paragraph><b>昼食</b> Lunch.</paragraph>
  <paragraph><b>朝食</b> Breakfast.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The one she held in her hands was marked similarly.</paragraph>
  <paragraph><b>夕食</b> Dinner.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Not a word. Not a note. Just this.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Someone had prepared the house for her. Cleaned the floors. Washed and lavendered the bedding. Stocked the soaps and creams. Dried the herbs. Peeled the garlic. Seasoned the pans. And cooked for her. Not like a stranger—like a caretaker. Like someone who expected her to come, and wanted her to feel… safe.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She pressed her fingertips gently to the foil, to the ink of her name. It felt too much. Too generous. Too kind.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>“Who?... “ she asked to the silence.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>And though the silence didn’t answer, it held her. And she let it.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She peeled back the foil slowly, careful not to tear it. Cool air spilled out from beneath the seal, carrying with it the faint scent of &lt;i&gt;shōyu&lt;/i&gt;—soy sauce—seaweed, and something softly earthy—rice, perhaps, laced with &lt;i&gt;dashi&lt;/i&gt;—The broth giving a rich umami scent to the grains, so full and savoury it made her mouth water in anticipation.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Nestled against the bed of seasoned rice lay delicate flakes of &lt;i&gt;tai&lt;/i&gt;—sea bream—glistening faintly in the low light. Bits of carrot and &lt;i&gt;konbu&lt;/i&gt;—seaweed—were scattered among the grains, their colours muted but warm in tone, like embers folded into the dish.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Even cold, it smelled… kind. Like something made with care, not obligation.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>A simple meal. Coastal. Humble. She smiled, just barely. She looked around, bowl still in hand, looking for an appliance to warm up her meal.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>There was no microwave.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Not on the counter. Not tucked into a corner. Not even a lonely blinking clock or a forgotten power cord to hint one had ever been there.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She checked anyway.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Cupboards. The narrow shelves above the breakfast bar. The low drawer near the fridge. Under the sink.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Nothing.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The only outlet she could see—barely—was the one behind the fridge. Probably original to the unit. Everything else was wood, enamel, iron, air. No buttons. No switches. No convenience.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The bowl still in her hands, she crossed the kitchen and set it gently on the counter—the chill of the ceramic biting faintly at her fingertips, enough to make her want to let go. She set it down before turning to face the stove.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She frowned, eyes drifting across its surface. It was old, its black enamel polished but worn with years of use. She turned one of the brass knobs experimentally, but nothing happened—not the familiar spark of electricity, nor the soft click of ignition.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her brow furrowed.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>But she could hear it—a soft hiss, steady and low. And smell it too. That sharp, metallic tang curling into the air.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her breath caught.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She let go of the knob immediately, stepping back as if the whole stove might suddenly erupt. The smell was stronger now, unmistakable. Her heart thudded once—hard—in her chest.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Gas.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She knew it was dangerous. Explosive. Poisonous. Something you weren’t supposed to mess with.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She waved a hand near her face, trying to fan the air, half-expecting a siren to go off or the house to start beeping at her.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Nothing happened.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Just the silence. The smell. And the absurd realisation that she didn’t actually know how to use this.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She swallowed, cheeks warming in quiet embarrassment.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Of course she didn’t.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her mind flashed back to her mother’s kitchen—her fingers flicking a switch near the oven before twisting the knob to release the gas. Instinctively, Misaki’s gaze roamed the edges of the stove, fingertips brushing the metal, searching for something—anything—that resembled a switch.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>There was nothing. Just black enamel and brass bolts.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She sighed, straightening up and glancing once more around the kitchen. And then she remembered—the box of matches she had spotted earlier, tucked into the corner of a small cabinet while searching for a socket. She hadn’t paid it much attention at the time. Just another oddity in a house that seemed determined to slow her down.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She stepped over to the cabinet, opened it, and found them again—a battered old box, nestled behind neat rows of tins and ceramic jars. Faded paper. Rough edges. Still half-full.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She stared at them, half-surprised. She couldn’t remember the last time she’d seen matches outside of a restaurant with their branded covers.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her fingers plucked one from the box, turning it over in her hand. The red tip flaked slightly, powdering her fingertips.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>&lt;i&gt;Alright, she thought, steeling herself.&lt;/i&gt;</paragraph>
  <paragraph>&lt;i&gt;She struck the match against the box. The flame sprang to life with a sudden flare of light and heat. Misaki stared at it for a moment—mesmerised by the way it danced, delicate and alive—before bringing it to the burner and turning the knob once more, half in fear of an explosion, half in hope.&lt;/i&gt;</paragraph>
  <paragraph>&lt;i&gt;The flame caught instantly.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;Blue and steady.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;It flared around the iron base in a perfect ring.&lt;/i&gt;</paragraph>
  <paragraph>&lt;i&gt;She let go of the knob, startled.&lt;/i&gt;</paragraph>
  <paragraph>&lt;i&gt;A soft click—then silence.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;The flame vanished.&lt;/i&gt;</paragraph>
  <paragraph>&lt;i&gt;The sensor hadn’t warmed up enough. The safety shutoff had triggered automatically.&lt;/i&gt;</paragraph>
  <paragraph>&lt;i&gt;She stared at the dark burner, lips pressed together.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;Progress… inexperience had ruined the moment.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;But still—progress.&lt;/i&gt;</paragraph>
  <paragraph>&lt;i&gt;She struck another match.&lt;/i&gt;</paragraph>
  <paragraph>&lt;i&gt;And tried again.&lt;/i&gt;</paragraph>
  <paragraph>This time, she held the knob in place—just for a second.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The flame caught. Held. Steady and blue.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her lips parted in triumph.「やった！」—&lt;i&gt;Success!&lt;/i&gt;—she whispered, half laughing. The word left her lips like breath, bright and involuntary.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>But the feeling faded almost as quickly as it had come, replaced by a flicker of uncertainty.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She’d never done this before—not really.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>In Tokyo, she had lived in glass towers, bathed in soft light and filtered air, the world delivered at the touch of a button. Meals were brought to her—at least before management decided she needed to weigh 42 kilos or less. Before the detox teas and the supplements. Her space was managed. Her life, curated. Wrapped in convenience. Sealed off from reality.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>But here…</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Here she was, striking matches like it was 1952—and lighting her own fire.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>A small victory. But it was hers.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She smiled, for real this time.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>And now here she was—striking matches like it was 1952.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>But her mind—ever a whirlwind—pressed the happiness down again, with more strength.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She leaned back against the counter, eyes fixed on the flame.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>&lt;i&gt;What am I doing?&lt;/i&gt;</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The question came unbidden, laced with the faint edge of doubt.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Living alone. Lighting her own stove. Warming up food in a pan.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>It was so far removed from the life she’d led, it almost felt like pretending.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>For years, she’d been made to believe she was something delicate. Elevated. Untouchable. A goddess in glass heels. Her hands too precious to soil, her body too sculpted to carry weight. Even her fingernails had been curated—polished, shaped, insured.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>They had turned her into a symbol. And in doing so, stripped her of the right to be useful.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Now, outside that bubble, she felt… untrained. Unequipped.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>&lt;i&gt;Useless&lt;/i&gt;, whispered the part of her that still echoed with their voices.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>But she wasn’t.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Not anymore.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She looked back at the flame, still flickering steady. It hadn’t been much. But it had been hers.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The thought lingered, heavy and unyielding. But she straightened her shoulders, drawing a deep breath that filled her lungs with the scent of cedar and iron. &lt;i&gt;I will have to learn,&lt;/i&gt; she resolved, turning away from the kettle and moving to the cabinets once again.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The thought lingered, heavy and unyielding.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>But she straightened her shoulders, drawing a deep breath that filled her lungs with the scent of cedar and iron.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>&lt;i&gt;I’ll have to learn,&lt;/i&gt; she told herself.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Then, without hesitating, she turned from the stove and reached for one of the cast iron pans hanging neatly from the wall.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>It came loose in her hands with a satisfying weight—but heavier than she expected. She let out a quiet grunt, tightening her grip with both hands. Her arms strained slightly under the load.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Too heavy for what it was. Or maybe she was just too weak.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She frowned. Probably the latter.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Agency life hadn’t exactly encouraged muscle. They’d fed her supplements, not strength. Air and tea and expectations.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She adjusted her stance, steadying herself.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>It didn’t matter.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She had the pan. She had the flame.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>And she was going to warm up her supper.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She set the pan on the burner with a dull clang, the iron base ringing faintly against the enamel stove. The handle was rough in her hands, solid and warm now from where it had caught the heat of the rising flame.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She lifted the ceramic bowl from the counter, its sides still cold against her fingertips, and gave the contents a final glance. Then, steadying herself, she tilted it carefully over the pan. The rice slid out in soft clumps, flecks of carrot and konbu scattering across the metal. A few flakes of sea bream clung stubbornly to the sides, and she coaxed them loose with the edge of a wooden spoon she’d found in a drawer.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>It was thick and round-ended—probably the wrong tool—but it was the only one she’d seen, and she wasn’t about to stop now.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>A soft hiss met her ears as the rice met the heat. She stirred gently, slow circles, watching the grains loosen and settle into the pan.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The smell began to rise—shōyu and dashi, rich with umami. Sea bream. Earth. It filled the kitchen slowly, like fog rolling in.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She inhaled, surprised by how comforting it was.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Then—something changed.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>A sharp scent, thin and bitter, cut through the warmth.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her eyes widened.&lt;i&gt;Burning.&lt;/i&gt;</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Panic surged.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She reached for the knob and twisted it hard to the left—only to watch the flame leap higher, flaring up around the sides of the pan with a sudden whoosh.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>“No—no—no—!” she gasped, heart pounding. She turned it the other way, fast—too far.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>&lt;i&gt;Click.&lt;/i&gt;</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The flame vanished.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The silence felt louder than the hiss that had come before.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She stood there, one hand still on the knob, the other gripping the spoon. The kitchen was still again, except for her breathing—too fast. Too sharp.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>&lt;i&gt;What is wrong with me?&lt;/i&gt;</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her chest tightened, a low ache blooming behind her ribs.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>And then she saw it.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>A blackened scrap of leaf had caught against the pan’s inner wall—where a bit of garnish must have spilled over the side as she poured. It had nestled into the ridges of the seasoned glaze, and singed the moment the iron got hot.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Not the rice. Not her mistake. Just… a moment of chaos, nothing more.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She let out a slow, shuddering breath.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>&lt;i&gt;Breathe in. Relax. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;You are&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt; learning&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;…&lt;/i&gt;</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She turned the knob again—more gently this time—and struck another match. The flame bloomed soft and blue.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She lowered it carefully, eyes steady, and placed the pan back on the stove. Stirred.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The rice loosened again, catching the warmth without resistance. Steam rose in slow ribbons. The scent returned—this time deeper, more open.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She lifted the spoon, blew on it, and tasted.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Perfect.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Not just good. Not just edible.&lt;i&gt;Perfect.&lt;/i&gt;</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She turned off the flame, let the spoon rest gently against the pan, and reached for a ceramic plate by the sink. Rinsed it. Warmed it under hot water. Dried it with a soft cloth.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Carefully, she spooned the rice onto the bowl, trying not to spill. Each motion deliberate, almost ceremonial.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She hesitated as she reached to clean the edge—then blinked. She wanted to wipe the rim of the ceramic, and then she realised.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her skin was bare, save for the panties clinging to her hips. A thin sheen of sweat had returned, beading faintly along her back and collarbones.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She looked down at herself, cheeks warming.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>&lt;i&gt;Am I seriously cooking half-naked? Isn’t this… dangerous?&lt;/i&gt;</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The thought struck her as absurd and quietly hilarious.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>But also true.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Hot oil. Open flame. Bare skin.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She looked toward the towel still folded on the chair across the room… then looked back at her meal.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>&lt;i&gt;I’ll be careful,&lt;/i&gt; she told herself, suppressing a grin. &lt;i&gt;Next time, I’ll wear something.&lt;/i&gt;</paragraph>
  <paragraph>For now, she wiped the plate clean with a corner of the cloth she’d used to dry it, then set it down with quiet pride.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>In a nearby drawer, she found a pair of chopsticks—they seemed new, made of white acrylic.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Then she brought her plate to the breakfast bar, sat down, and placed the chopsticks beside it. The kitchen light caught the steam curling from the food.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She folded her hands, bowed her head.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>“Thank you,” she murmured. To Saitō. To whoever had cooked. To the kami watching over this strange, quiet house. To herself.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She lifted the chopsticks. Picked up the first bite.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The warmth hit her tongue and spread outward like breath across her skin.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She closed her eyes. The sea bream was soft. The rice clung just slightly to her teeth. The carrot gave the faintest crunch. The konbu carried something deeper—almost like the tide.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She chewed slowly, tasting everything.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The silence around her didn’t feel empty anymore.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>It felt… shared.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She smiled. A quiet, private thing.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She didn’t need to rush.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Not tonight.</paragraph>
  <paragraph></paragraph>
  <paragraph>Part 3 - The Ritual of Tea</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She finished the last bite slowly, chewing with care, her thoughts trailing far behind her taste buds. Her body felt warm now, soothed. Fed. Anchored.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>A cup of tea, she thought. That would be perfect.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She stood and gathered her things—the wooden spoon, the ceramic bowl, the plate with the faintest smudge of soy glaze. The chopsticks clinked gently against the rim as she carried everything to the sink.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The water ran clear and cold, the kind that bit at her fingers until they numbed, but she didn’t mind. She scrubbed with intention, rinsed well, dried each item with the cloth hung nearby. Then, still unaware of the crime against cast iron she was committing, she added soap to the pan. Suds bloomed, fragrant and thick, as she worked her sponge over the blackened surface. She wrinkled her nose a little—was that the right smell? Something earthy and… metallic?</paragraph>
  <paragraph>It didn’t matter. She rinsed it clean, dried it with the same cloth, and hung it carefully back on its hook.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Then, almost ceremonially, she reached for the kettle.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>It was heavier than it looked, all iron and belly, like a teapot from an older world. She filled it from the tap and set it atop the burner, striking a match with confidence this time. The flame obeyed instantly. Blue, obedient, waiting.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She adjusted the knob with ease.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>&lt;i&gt;Look at me now&lt;/i&gt;, she thought, lips curving into a smile. &lt;i&gt;A girl who makes fire&lt;/i&gt;.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Steam hadn’t yet begun to rise, but she turned, eyes scanning the kitchen.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>&lt;i&gt;Time to find the tea&lt;/i&gt;.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The first cabinet she opened held cups of various sizes—delicate porcelain with faded floral patterns, stout ceramic bowls, each stacked with care. She moved to the next, sliding it open to reveal something else entirely.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>There, nestled between stacks of tea towels, sat an aluminium container, polished to a high shine. Her fingertips brushed its surface, the designs engraved in sweeping curves and sharp edges. A cliffside stretched along its circumference, the house she now occupied etched into its centre, its windows tiny flecks of silver. Butterflies fluttered in mid-air, their wings frozen in graceful arcs, while the sea swirled at the base, each wave meticulously detailed. It was beautiful—an artwork hidden in plain sight.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Misaki ran her thumb along the lid’s edge before lifting it carefully. The faint scent of earth and green filtered up to greet her, rich and potent. Inside, powdered &lt;i&gt;matcha&lt;/i&gt; lay pressed against the sides, its surface smooth and untouched.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her eyes drifted back to the cabinet, where something else caught her attention. Beside the container lay a small bamboo scoop—its handle curved, its base shaped to measure just the right amount of powder. She held it up, the name surfacing from some quiet corner of memory. &lt;i&gt;Chashaku&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;.&lt;/i&gt; She wasn’t sure where she had learned it—but it stayed with her, the word soft on her tongue, reverent.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Next to it, resting in a lacquered wooden box, was a bamboo whisk, its tines delicate and curved inward. &lt;i&gt;Chasen,&lt;/i&gt; she recalled, the word flitting back like a loose thread of memory. And beside it, a simple tea bowl. &lt;i&gt;“&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;Chawan&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;,”&lt;/i&gt; she muttered to herself. It was wide and smooth, the glaze uneven but charming. She cradled it in her hands for a moment, feeling its weight, before setting it on the counter.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The kettle began to whistle, steam curling from its spout like silk threads unravelling. Misaki turned off the burner with a twist of her wrist, pouring the hot water into the bowl to warm it before emptying it out again. She moved slowly, deliberately, her motions unpractised but careful—guided not by skill, but recollection.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Then it came back to her.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>It had been just over a year ago, after her Kyoto concert on the &lt;i&gt;Magical Mirai 2&lt;/i&gt; tour. The &lt;i&gt;ryokan&lt;/i&gt; she stayed at had arranged a tea ceremony in one of its private &lt;i&gt;tatami&lt;/i&gt; rooms—a gesture of refinement, of prestige, meant to flatter the agency and impress their rising star.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She remembered the geisha—Shōko, in a pale blue kimono, her movements as fluid as water. Her face had been painted in the traditional style: porcelain skin, crimson lips, darkened brows like brushstrokes on silk. Beautiful, yes—but it wasn’t her face that Misaki had found arresting.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>It was the way she moved.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The way her sleeves draped like falling snow as she prepared the tea. The way she bowed, hands folded, hair gleaming in the light. Every gesture slow, deliberate, without effort. Grace incarnate.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Misaki had felt… something. Not quite attraction, not exactly. More like a tremble beneath the surface. A kind of hush inside her chest she hadn’t known was possible. A strange, light ache as she watched the woman kneel, whisk the tea, and serve it with a quiet smile.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Not quite desire. Not exactly. More like a hush beneath her skin, a pulse that paused to watch.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>It was one of the only moments in her idol life that hadn’t felt performative. Not part of the schedule. Not another smile rehearsed in a mirror. Just the warmth of steam, the scent of tea, and gestures that meant something.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She had been so taken by it that, days later—back in Tokyo, during one of her rare, almost countable free evenings—she asked Megumi to pick up a DVD about tea ceremonies and geisha tradition. A documentary, she said. Megumi didn’t ask questions. She brought it the next morning and left it by the television without comment.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>That night, Misaki stayed up to watch it. That’s where she learned the names of the tools. That’s why this moment felt sacred.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>There had been nothing scheduled for the following day—an almost unheard-of luxury—so she let herself fall into it completely. The way the women moved. The silence that breathed between their gestures. The choreography of grace and restraint. She watched it twice.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>And she remembered thinking, in a moment of startling clarity, that if her life had been different, she might have wanted to be a geisha.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Not for the makeup. Not for the mystery.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>But for the grace.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>And now, standing barefoot in this old kitchen, whisk in hand, sea air curling through the open window, she tried to follow those gestures—not perfectly, not beautifully, but sincerely.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>And this time, for herself.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She measured the matcha with the &lt;i&gt;chashaku&lt;/i&gt;, its pale bamboo scooping the powder with a kind of elegance she didn’t quite feel. One scoop. Two. The matcha settled into the base of the bowl—vibrant, unyielding. She poured the water slowly, watching as the green powder swirled and dispersed, softening into clouds of emerald.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The &lt;i&gt;chasen&lt;/i&gt; felt foreign in her hands, its delicate tines pressing against the liquid as she whisked. Her movements were clumsy at first, droplets splashing over the rim. But she adjusted, tightening her grip, flicking her wrist with more control. Froth began to form—thin, uneven, but present. She watched as it settled, tiny bubbles catching the light before dissolving into the surface.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She paused, staring down at her creation. The tea was bright green, flecks of matcha dust still clinging to the edges of the &lt;i&gt;chawan&lt;/i&gt;. It wasn’t perfect—far from it—but it was real. Made with her own hands.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>And just before she brought it to her lips, the memory unfurled.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She saw it again, sudden and clear—the way Shōko had bowed, her forehead nearly touching the floor, her sleeves spilling like a waterfall onto the &lt;i&gt;tatami&lt;/i&gt;. Her hands motionless, her back curved with reverence. The silence of the room had thickened in that moment, heavy with intention.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>And she had bowed to her. Hatsune Miku. The idol, the goddess almost.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Not to the agency or the room or the title. To her.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Even now, Misaki could feel it—how everything had gone still. The other idols around her had felt it too. Rin and Len had giggled softly, not out of mockery, but overwhelmed by the sheer intensity of the moment. Luka, she was sure, had tears in her eyes, her fingers pressed to her lips. Kaito was visibly flushed, eyes shining, the line between arousal and reverence blurred. Meiko was yawning from exhaustion, but her gaze never left Shōko's hands.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>It had been a performance—but one that belonged to tradition. One that touched something deeper than applause. Shōko made it something sacred, and it was an offering to Miku—the goddess of music.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Everyone had always acted like she was one, of course—on stage, in ads, on billboards. But never like that. Never with such grace, such reverence, such complete, deliberate beauty.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Now, in this quiet kitchen by the sea, Misaki brought the bowl to her lips. Blew gently across its surface, the way Shōko had done. And drank.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>It wasn’t good. Not really. Bitter, slightly gritty, the foam already collapsing. But she drank it all the same, letting the warmth slide down her throat, slow and steady, as if it might root her a little deeper into the floor beneath her feet. She glanced back at the kettle, steam still trickling from the spout, and smiled softly to herself.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>&lt;i&gt;I’ll learn,&lt;/i&gt; she thought. &lt;i&gt;Eventually.&lt;/i&gt;</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She sat in silence for a moment, the bowl cradled in her hands, the aftertaste of memory soft on her tongue. Not just the tea—but Shōko’s bow, the weight of reverence, the fragile ache of being seen as more than a symbol. The silence around her no longer felt hollow. It felt shared. Held. She closed her eyes.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Part 4 - The Letter Unsealed</paragraph>
  <paragraph>And that was when it came back.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Not the memory of Kyoto—but the envelope.</paragraph>
  <paragraph></paragraph>
  <paragraph>It rose in her mind like a candle re-lit, quiet and insistent.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She set the bowl down carefully on the counter, the green residue still clinging to the ceramic’s edge, and rose to her feet. Her chest tightened with the shift in thought. Her hands, no longer trembling, now moved with a different kind of care.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She crossed the kitchen and stepped back into the living room, toward the letter she hadn’t yet dared to open.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>It was still there, resting on the low wooden table, the wax seal unbroken, its crimson hue catching the warm light of the room. The butterfly wings glimmered, frozen mid-flight, and the cherry blossoms seemed to drift ever so slightly in the stillness.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Misaki reached for it, fingers brushing the edge of the wax. Her breath was steady, slow. She slid her nail under the edge of the seal, feeling it crack with a soft pop. The envelope gave way, its folds parting to reveal a key and a piece of paper, folded with care.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She turned the envelope upside down, letting the key fall into her palm. It heavy, iron, its handle twisted into the shape of wings.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>It was followed by the note, folded with careful precision, ink pressed neatly into the surface. Misaki stared at them both, her heart a steady drumbeat in her chest.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She paused there, her fingers curling instinctively around the weight. There was a strange intimacy to the moment. This wasn’t a package. It wasn’t a delivery. It was personal. Someone had sealed this for her.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She unfolded the paper carefully, the &lt;i&gt;washi&lt;/i&gt; thick and textured beneath her fingertips. The ink had been pressed in clean, deliberate strokes, each character drawn with the elegance of someone well-practised in the art of handwriting. Her eyes drifted over the kanji, her mind grasping at familiar shapes and symbols, the faint echoes of her school lessons tugging at her memory.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>It was not just a note, a letter. This was supposed to be a &lt;i&gt;Goshuin&lt;/i&gt;, It had the seal of the shrine, the same one embroiled in the &lt;i&gt;omamori&lt;/i&gt;. The same pressed in the wax seal.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>A Goshuin. A temple stamp, but this wasn’t from any pilgrimage. This was a message wrapped in ritual. One meant only for her.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The paper felt textured beneath her fingertips, almost fibrous, carrying the faint scent of cedar and ink. Her eyes moved slowly over the delicate strokes, each character meticulously drawn, breathing elegance and purpose.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>::tg::</paragraph>
  <paragraph>蝶の楽園へようこそ。</paragraph>
  <paragraph>竹林の中、神社へ続く</paragraph>
  <paragraph>石段の麓にある郵便箱</paragraph>
  <paragraph>はあなたのものです。</paragraph>
  <paragraph>添付された鍵を使っ</paragraph>
  <paragraph>て開けてください。</paragraph>
  <paragraph>よろしくお願いします。</paragraph>
  <paragraph>竹の森の入口の友より。::/tg::</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Misaki's breath stilled, her fingers brushing the edge of the paper as if to anchor herself. The first line rippled through her mind like a whispered incantation. &lt;i&gt;Welcome to Butterfly Heaven.&lt;/i&gt; She read it again, slower this time, each word sinking into her like stones cast into still water.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her eyes trailed down to the final line, where the ink curled into a name—no, not a name. A title, a symbol.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>竹の森の入口の友より&lt;i&gt;—A Friend from the Bamboo Forest Entrance.&lt;/i&gt;</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her gaze drifted back to the characters pressed into the paper. Her mind traced the strokes of the kanji that lingered there. &lt;i&gt;Take&lt;/i&gt; (竹) and &lt;i&gt;Guchi&lt;/i&gt; (口)—the symbols almost whispering the memory of Saitō-san’s voice, the way he had spoken of Kamiyama Cove with reverence, with nostalgia.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>&lt;i&gt;Takeguchi&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her breath caught, fingers pressing against the edge of the note. &lt;i&gt;A friend of &lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;Saitō&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;-&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;san&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;…&lt;/i&gt; It struck her like a ripple spreading outwards, the realisation unfurling in slow, deliberate waves. The envelope, the seal, the letter—they were from someone who knew him. Someone who knew her arrival, who had left this for her to find.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The key sat heavy in her palm, its surface smooth and cool to the touch. She lifted it carefully, holding it up to the light. It was made of black iron, aged and intricate, with a handle shaped like the wings of a butterfly. The delicate arches and carved patterns seemed to shimmer in the low light, catching the edges of sunlight streaming through the window.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>&lt;i&gt;Who makes something like this?&lt;/i&gt; she wondered.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her thumb traced the curve of the wings, marvelling at the craftsmanship. It wasn’t just a key—it was art. The body was sturdy, its teeth jagged and purposeful, but the handle… the handle was breathtaking. The butterfly wings flared out elegantly, casted with veins that mimicked the real thing, almost as if it would flutter out of her hand if she so much as loosened her grip.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Misaki held it up, tilting it. She wondered how many hands had held it before hers, how many locks it had turned, how many secrets it had kept.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>And more pressingly—what it would open.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her gaze flickered back to the letter, the words still fresh in her mind. “The mailbox at the feet of the stone stairs to the Shrine in the grove is yours.  &lt;i&gt;Use the attached key to open it.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;”&lt;/i&gt;</paragraph>
  <paragraph>It was confusing and yet… exciting. Her pulse thrummed faintly beneath her skin, the room around her fading into the periphery. Her mind conjured the image of the stone steps, the long stretch of bamboo leading up to the shrine. A mailbox, hidden away at the foot of the path, waiting for her.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The image glowed in her mind like something from a fairy tale.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>&lt;i&gt;I’m going to find it,&lt;/i&gt; she thought, breath catching at the idea. She traced the key’s handle once more before setting it down gently on the table beside the envelope, its weight still lingering in her hand.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Misaki moved back towards the window, her fingers brushing the paper to slide it open peering out. Shadows clung to the bamboo grove, stretching long and sharp against the earth. It was darker than she expected. The kind of darkness that pressed against the glass, folding the landscape into shadowy silhouettes.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her eyes traced the line of the path that led back to the main road, the gravel walkway barely visible beneath the thick canopy of branches. The trees crowded together, their limbs weaving into a canopy that swallowed the light. She could hear the faint rustle of leaves, the whisper of wind through the stalks, but there was no light—no glow of streetlamps or distant signs. Only darkness.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She chewed her bottom lip, her eyes scanning the edges of the grove, looking for any flicker of light, any sign of life. There was none. The thought of venturing out alone, through those trees in the pitch black, sent a shiver down her spine.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>A shiver—half fear, half thrill.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Sliding the window closed once more, she stepped back into the room. The envelope and key still lay on the low table, casting a soft shadow under the dim light. Her gaze lingered there for a moment before she shook her head. &lt;i&gt;Not now.&lt;/i&gt;</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Part 5 – The Communion</paragraph>
  <paragraph>For now, her stomach felt full, content in a way she hadn’t expected. She straightened, stretching out the tension in her back before moving back towards the genkan where her suitcase laid.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She rummaged through the once neatly folded clothes and travel necessities, fingers brushing over familiar objects before finding what she sought—a simple toothbrush, white and unadorned, and a small tube of toothpaste. She held them in her hand for a moment, staring down at them with a faint smile. &lt;i&gt;I’m really doing this,&lt;/i&gt; she thought, feeling a flutter of disbelief that she had made it this far.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Misaki padded back to the kitchen, the boards creaking softly beneath her feet. She twisted the tap, letting the water run clear and cold before she cupped her hand beneath it, dampening the bristles. The faucet sputtered slightly, the pipes groaning with age, but the water ran steady.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She squeezed a line of toothpaste onto the brush and began to clean her teeth, moving with slow, deliberate strokes.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The taste of mint spread over her tongue, sharp and cool. She brushed with care, feeling the remnants of rice, fish and seaweed wash away with each movement. </paragraph>
  <paragraph>In the quiet of the kitchen, the act felt almost meditative, like she was washing away not just the remnants of dinner, but the dust of the past few days—the grime of travel, the uncertainty of her new surroundings.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>When she finished, she cupped her hands under the stream, splashing her face, rinsing out her mouth until she tasted only water. Misaki dried her hands on a small cloth hanging near the sink, folding it neatly back into place before turning off the light and heading towards the staircase.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The stairs creaked beneath her weight, the wood groaning like it hadn’t been tread on in some time. She moved slowly, trailing her hand along the banister, its surface smooth and worn by years of use. The sound of crickets drifted through the windows, mingling with the whisper of wind through the bamboo grove outside. It was soothing, almost ethereal, like the house itself was breathing along with the world.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>At the top of the stairs, the hallway stretched out before her, narrow and intimate, the walls lined with faint marks of age and wear. She stepped lightly across the wooden planks, pausing just before the &lt;i&gt;shōji&lt;/i&gt; door that led to her bedroom. The paper screen glowed softly with the last threads of evening light, casting faint shadows against the floor.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Misaki slid the door open with a soft whisper of wood against wood, stepping into the room that she had rushed from earlier. She blinked at the sight of the futon, still half-sprawled across the floor, blankets tangled from her hurried exit.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>A giggle slipped from her lips, soft and genuine. &lt;i&gt;I must've looked so ridiculous,&lt;/i&gt; she thought, pressing a hand to her mouth to stifle the laughter that bubbled up. She took a breath, composing herself, and stepped further into the room, her fingers combing through her hair out of habit.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her hand paused mid-motion, catching on strands that ended far sooner than she was accustomed to. She stared at her reflection in the darkened windowpane, the hazelnut strands brushing her shoulders, cut clean and sharp. She touched it gently, feeling the soft edges against her fingertips. &lt;i&gt;I really did it…&lt;/i&gt;</paragraph>
  <paragraph>A slow exhale left her, carrying with it the weight of old memories. &lt;i&gt;I’m Misaki now,&lt;/i&gt; she reminded herself, the name settling on her tongue like something sacred, something new. &lt;i&gt;Miku&lt;/i&gt; was a ghost of a life she no longer belonged to. Here, she was someone else—someone with shorter hair, simpler clothes, and hands that now lit their own stoves.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Misaki reached for the edge of the futon, smoothing out the blankets and straightening the pillows. She moved slowly, methodically, brushing out the creases and fluffing the thin mattress before kneeling down to slide beneath the sheets.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The linen was soft, freshly laundered, carrying the faint scent of sun and wind. She nestled deeper, the cool fabric pressing against her skin, wrapping her in gentle weight. Her hands slid beneath the pillow, cradling her head as she stared up at the ceiling, its wooden beams casting faint shadows in the moonlight that slipped through the open window.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The sheets were crisp, a quiet balm against the lingering heat of summer. She shifted slightly, the warmth clinging to her limbs. Then, slowly, with the same careful deliberation that had guided her all evening, she slid her underwear down her hips, inch by inch, until it slipped past her knees and caught at her ankle. A subtle kick sent it beyond the futon’s edge, leaving her bare beneath the covers.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The linen kissed her skin with cool relief, her body now freed of even the last small barrier. It wasn’t sensual—It was something simpler. More human. A moment of privacy so complete, it almost felt sacred.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She exhaled softly, feeling alive.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>A breeze drifted in, salty and cool, sweeping through the room with a whisper of the sea. It threaded through her hair, brushing over her cheeks, carrying with it the distant rumbling of waves and the rustle of bamboo leaves. Misaki closed her eyes, breathing it in, letting it fill her lungs and settle in her chest.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her body relaxed, sinking further into the futon, tension unwinding from her limbs as she let herself fall into the stillness. It felt strange and new—this quiet, this solitude. There was no hum of neon lights, no distant roar of traffic, just the steady song of the night outside her window.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her hand brushed over her stomach, her fingers tracing the faint ridges of her ribs. She had gotten thinner—her frame sharper than she remembered. A thought flickered at the edges of her mind. &lt;i&gt;I &lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;need to&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt; gain some weight&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;…&lt;/i&gt; The idea warmed her, settling into her bones with a strange sort of resolve. &lt;i&gt;Yes,&lt;/i&gt; she thought, drifting on the edge of sleep. &lt;i&gt;I want to look… normal. Healthy.&lt;/i&gt;</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The sea breeze swirled once more, ruffling the curtains and whispering against her skin. Misaki sighed softly, the breath easing out of her lungs as her eyelids grew heavier, the weight of the day pressing her gently down. The last thing she heard before slipping into a light sleep was the sigh of the wind and the distant murmur of the waves.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>But then—she opened her eyes.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>A distant caw broke the quiet. A gull, maybe. She would have to get used to that sound. But it wasn’t the bird that caught her attention.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>It was the sky.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>A shimmer just beyond the frame of the open window. Something distant, something calling.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She stood suddenly—like a wire had snapped. The blanket slipped from her shoulders, forgotten. Completely bare, she crossed the room, fingers brushing the windowsill as she leaned forward and looked up.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The stars.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Not just a handful of them—but all of them. Scattered across the firmament in shimmering arcs. The Milky Way unfurled like a ribbon of silver fire, stretching from one horizon to the other. She could see the planets again—steady, vigilant, ancient. Guardians watching over the sea.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her breath caught.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her hand rose to the window frame, just as it had that night in Tokyo—the night she escaped. She remembered how Saitō had stilled beside her, how he’d simply watched as she stood spellbound by the blackout sky. &lt;i&gt;Light pollution hides things,&lt;/i&gt; he had said. &lt;i&gt;Beautiful things.&lt;/i&gt; And then, quietly, as though promising her something sacred—&lt;i&gt;At Kamiyama Cove, you will see skies like this almost every night&lt;/i&gt;.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>And here they were.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Not imagined. Not distant. Not behind a tinted lens. But real. Present. Infinite.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her heart swelled—not with sadness, not even with wonder, but with something hotter, sharper. The unshakable thrill of arrival.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Without a second thought, without the burden of self-consciousness, she spun on her heel and sprinted across the room’s tatami. Down the hall, breathless. Her bare feet padded fast against the floorboards, each step a thrill, a laugh just barely suppressed. She darted down the narrow stairs, the handrail rushing past, her hand barely brushing it. Her hair streamed behind her.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She nearly tripped at the landing, caught herself, kept going.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>No shoes. No robe. No hesitation.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The &lt;i&gt;shōji&lt;/i&gt; door to the &lt;i&gt;genkan&lt;/i&gt; slid open with a rush. She didn’t bother with sandals. Her feet kissed the wood of the &lt;i&gt;engawa&lt;/i&gt;, then leapt down into the garden below.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The cool earth met her skin like water, damp and alive, and she ran—skyclad and joyous—past the stone path, past the moss-covered rocks, until she reached the open edge of the clearing.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>There, with nothing between her and the sky, she stopped and looked up.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>And gave herself to the stars.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Not as an idol. Not as a girl. Not as anyone expected her to be.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>But simply as Misaki.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She stood in the moonlit garden, naked and laughing, running in small circles with her arms extended, her gaze never leaving the firmament. The grass brushing her calves, her arms wide, the night air wrapping around her like a second skin.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>And for the first time since arriving in Kamiyama Cove, she felt completely, breathtakingly free.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The laughter faded from her lips, gentled by awe. Her knees bent slowly, and she let herself down—first to a crouch, then to the earth. The grass was cool and damp against her skin, the soil soft beneath her. She lay back without hesitation, the warmth of her body folding into the night’s breath.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The breeze rolled over her like a sigh from the sea, tasting of salt and summer and distant blossoms. It brushed along her bare legs, her stomach, her collarbones—never crude, never cruel. Just &lt;i&gt;present.&lt;/i&gt; Like the wind knew she was here and approved.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She inhaled deeply, and the world filled her.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Cedar. Earth. The faint iron of the sea. Somewhere, far off, the low chirr of bell crickets carried on the air. A frog croaked from the edge of the garden. A soft rustle in the trees—the bamboo speaking to the dark.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She opened her eyes to the sky.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The stars stared back.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>No ceiling. No glass. No velvet rope of backstage dressing rooms. Just the cosmos above and the grass below, and her body—her whole, imperfect, sacred body—laid bare in the middle.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She didn’t flinch.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She didn’t cover herself.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She let them see her. She &lt;i&gt;wanted&lt;/i&gt; them to see.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The stars didn’t judge. They didn’t ask anything of her. They just watched, as they always had. Patient. Steady. Eternal.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>And as she stared back, she began to feel it.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The &lt;i&gt;movement.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt; &lt;/i&gt;Not of the stars themselves—but of the earth.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The slow, ancient turning beneath her spine. The invisible breath of a planet in motion, carrying her with it. She could &lt;i&gt;feel&lt;/i&gt; it—not metaphor, not poetry, but a real, physical truth. A low hum inside her bones, inside her blood. She was lying on a spinning sphere, hurtling through darkness, and everything in her had gone &lt;i&gt;still.&lt;/i&gt;</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She let her arms spread out beside her. Her fingers brushed the stalks, the dampness clinging to her skin. Her hair fanned out like seaweed on a current. Her eyes stayed open.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>“I’m here,” she whispered. Not to anyone in particular. Just to the world. To the stars. To herself.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>“I’m really here.”</paragraph>
  <paragraph>And the stars shimmered in reply—silent, ancient, and achingly bright.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>It was a communion—but also something deeper. A surrender. A merging.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She felt herself open—not just her body, but her breath, her presence, her “self”. As though she had unfastened every clasp that held her together and offered it all—skin and soul—to the wind and the stars.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The grass caressed her body, swaying beneath her, whispering across her skin. It touched her &lt;i&gt;everywhere&lt;/i&gt;—beneath her knees, between her thighs, brushing the crease where hip met waist. Kissed the base of her spine, the curve of her tailbone, the inner seams of her thighs, touched her with reverence, lovingly. And above, the wind joined in—cool and delicate—ghosting over the slope of her belly, the underside of her breasts, circling each tip until they tightened in response.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She didn’t flinch. She didn’t cover herself.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>It didn’t feel wrong. It felt… worshipful.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Like the world wasn’t looking &lt;i&gt;at&lt;/i&gt; her, but &lt;i&gt;through&lt;/i&gt; her—seeing her not as girl or goddess, but as something a part of itself. Elemental. Flesh made of breath and tide.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She breathed it in. Let herself be known. Let the earth take her. And unlike that horrible night, it did not feel like it was breaking her. It felt like it was making her whole. </paragraph>
  <paragraph>She let out a soft breath, a tremble on her lips—not of pleasure, but presence. Like the exhale of someone remembered by the world. And the stars shimmered in reply.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She had never been touched like this—not by hands, but by the very rhythm of the world. It moved through her, around her, within her. Not to take, not to own—but to welcome.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>And she welcomed it in turn.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>It wasn’t erotic. It was elemental. Not passion, but &lt;b&gt;participation&lt;/b&gt;.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She wasn’t alone under the sky. She was &lt;i&gt;with&lt;/i&gt; it. &lt;i&gt;In&lt;/i&gt; it.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>It did not need a name. It did not need a purpose.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Only this sky. This breath. This earth beneath her. This wind around her. This warmth inside her.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>And the knowledge that she was no longer lost.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The sensation rose slowly—quiet as mist. Not from her skin, but from somewhere inside it. A pressure without pain. A pull without direction. Something vast and ancient stirring in her chest, as though a door had been opened in a place she never knew existed.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The wind curled beneath her shoulders, lifting not her body but something deeper—an awareness, a trembling clarity. Her breath caught—not from effort, not from exertion, but from the overwhelming stillness of it all. The sky seemed to draw nearer. Or perhaps she had risen to meet it.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Goosebumps rose softly along her arms, her neck, the backs of her thighs. Not from cold, but from something wordless. Like the echo of a voice not yet heard.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She did not cry. She did not move. But something inside her—unseen, unnamed—expanded. An apotheosis of her soul and the cosmos.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She let go of the self she thought she had to be, and what remained was not empty. It was whole, quiet and infinite.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>And in that silence, the stars above her did not speak—but they listened. And she smiled.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Because for the first time in her life, she had nothing left to prove.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>And everything still to become.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She closed her eyes.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>And for a heartbeat—no, for something beyond time—she felt it.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>A stillness so complete it hummed.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>It wasn’t like before. That time had been sharp and brutal, a trespass masked as devotion, her body’s betrayal used against her, its response twisted into shame. That night had left something inside her shattered—confused, silenced, raw.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>But this…</paragraph>
  <paragraph>This was different.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Nothing was being done &lt;i&gt;to&lt;/i&gt; her. No hand, no voice, no presence imposing. The stars did not ask her to perform. The wind did not demand she pretend. The grass did not invade—they only touched what she had already offered.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>And she had offered everything.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Not out of fear. Not because she was told to.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Because she &lt;i&gt;wanted&lt;/i&gt; to. Because something in her longed to be known—not desired, not devoured—but &lt;i&gt;understood&lt;/i&gt;. And the night, in all its terrible vastness, accepted her without condition.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>A breath shuddered through her—not from fear, but from release.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>A tingle ran across her skin—goosebumps, not from cold, but from awe. The kind of awe that makes your chest ache. That makes your ribs feel too small for the life inside them.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her heart beat slow and steady, yet her mind swam, suspended. As if her consciousness were diffusing into the stars themselves.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>And then came the peak—quiet, luminous, breathtaking.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Not a climax of flesh, but of &lt;i&gt;soul&lt;/i&gt;. Not something that happened &lt;i&gt;to&lt;/i&gt; her, but something she rose into—unshackled, weightless.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The night did not break her.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>It built her.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Whole.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She stayed there for minutes... maybe hours. The stars above her had shifted—another constellation now watched from the velvet black, familiar yet new. Time had passed. And she didn’t feel shame. Not for her body. Not for her stillness. Not even for being seen.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She sat up slowly, the grass whispering against her spine as she rose. The sea stretched out before her, silvered by moonlight, calm and endless. It looked like breath held in a bowl of night. And then—she saw it.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>At first, she thought it was a firefly. But it was too large. Its wings too slow. Too luminous.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>It drifted past the old cherry tree near the edge of the clearing—and as it did, something impossible happened.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The tree lit up beneath its glow. Not with flame, but with life.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Petals unfurled where none had been. Branches blushed with sudden bloom. A soft pink spread like a breath through the canopy—as though spring had returned, if only for a heartbeat.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>No cherry tree should bloom this late into summer. Yet this one did, as the light passed through it.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>And then the butterfly moved on. Its glow slipped from the branches. And the leaves returned to their deep, summer green.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Its wings shimmered—gold, then blue, then amethyst, then rose—each colour folding into the next like oil on water. Iridescent. Impossible.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>A lone butterfly, glowing like starlight made flesh, gliding through the warm air as though gravity were an afterthought.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>It passed over the garden and into the bamboo grove, trailing brilliance behind it. Not dust, pollen, not even Sakura petals, but shine. A thread of gold pulled gently through the night, as if it were stitching something closed.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her breath caught. She rubbed her eyes. Once. Twice. And when her vision cleared—it was gone.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The grove was quiet again. But something inside her was not.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>“I must be hallucinating from tiredness,” she murmured, trying to laugh—but the sound came out too softly. Too reverently. Like an apology to the dark. “Or… from whatever it is the night and I just did.”</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She shifted slightly—then stilled. A faint warmth lingered between her thighs. Not sweat. Not dew. But a trace of something unmistakably her own. A soft, silken echo of presence. </paragraph>
  <paragraph>Her cheeks flushed—not with shame, exactly, but with startled wonder.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She hadn’t meant to…Had she?</paragraph>
  <paragraph>It hadn’t been &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt;, not really. She hadn’t touched herself. She hadn’t needed to. And yet, her body had responded. Gently. Fully. Unbidden.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>To the air, to the stars, to the earth beneath her. They had touched something in her no one ever had. And something deep within had answered.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She didn’t name it. She didn’t need to.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>It was just another truth of the night, sacred, quiet… hers.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>A small giggle slipped out—warm, breathless, unashamed.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>It didn’t feel wrong, didn’t even feel erotic. It felt... good.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Ever since that night in Gunma, she hadn’t come close to this kind of release. She hadn’t even thought herself capable of it. She wasn’t ready. Maybe she never would be. And she was sure that wasn’t what this was.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>This was a thing of the soul, a communion. A covenant between the night and her. And the sky had kept its promise.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Whatever it was, it had shifted something in her. And though she knew—deep inside—that it was only temporary, still… the ache in her chest—the one that had lived there since that night in Gunma, when everything was taken from her—it ebbed.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Not vanished. But softened as if something had leaned close to it and whispered,&lt;i&gt;“You’re not alone.”&lt;/i&gt;</paragraph>
  <paragraph>Misaki stood, brushing dew from her thighs. The grass clung in small, stubborn kisses. The breeze followed her as she retraced her steps—slowly, gently—as if the earth itself urged her not to rush.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She climbed the steps to the &lt;i&gt;engawa&lt;/i&gt;, passed beneath the portal, and slid closed the door she had left open. She stepped barefoot onto the wooden floor—not cold, not warm. Just home.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She made her way to the &lt;i&gt;ofuro&lt;/i&gt;, where she used one of the wall nozzles to cleanse the soles of her feet, the bits of grass clinging to her calves, and the warmth that still lingered between her thighs—a trace of the night’s strange communion.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She washed herself gently, reverently. Not out of shame, but as one might rinse a chalice after a ceremony. Thankful for the gift, but wishing to enter the arms of sleep fresh, clean—ready for another kind of intimacy. The one shared between sheets, pillows and sleep.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She dried herself slowly, tenderly, then returned to her bedroom, where the futon awaited—quiet, untouched, forgiving.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>She slid beneath the covers. The linen whispered against her skin, the breeze curled around her shoulders once more, this time like a lullaby.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>And her eyes closed without hesitation.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The last thing she felt was not pain, not fear, but gratitude.</paragraph>
  <paragraph>The darkness took her, and she took the darkness in return. In that embrace—between the stillness, the song of the night, the stars as sentinels and the moon as witness—she slept.</paragraph>
  <paragraph></paragraph>
</document>
